const topics = {
  "Indian Constitution": {
    questions: [
      {
        question: "The constitution was implemented on : ?",
        options: [
          "15th August 1947",
          "26th January 1950",
          "5th November 1949",
          "26th October 1999",
        ],
        answer: "26th January 1950",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Who was the chairman of drafting committe ?",
        options: [
          "Dr.B.R. Ambedkar",
          "Md Sajid",
          "Dr. Rajendra Prasad",
          "Jawahaelal Nehru",
        ],
        answer: "Dr.B.R. Ambedkar",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Who can form the state cabinet ?",
        options: [
          "Chief minister",
          "Governor",
          "Deputy chief minister",
          "Chief Security of state",
        ],
        answer: "Chief minister",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "How many originals articles contained in Indian Constitution ?",
        options: [
          "350 Articles",
          "448 Articles",
          "395 Articles",
          "398 Articles",
        ],
        answer: "395 Articles",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "President is the __________ ?",
        options: [
          "Real exective head",
          "Nominal exective head",
          "Government head",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "Nominal exective head",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "How many menbers are nominated to Rajya Saba.?",
        options: ["10", "11", "13", "12"],
        answer: "12",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Who is the commander in Chief of the Armed Force.?",
        options: [
          "President",
          "Vice-president",
          "Prime minister",
          "chief minister",
        ],
        answer: "President",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Who appoints the supereme court judges?",
        options: [
          "Prime minister",
          "Parliament",
          "Vice-president",
          "President",
        ],
        answer: "President",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "The period of Gram Panchayat is __________?",
        options: ["2 Years", "4 Years", "6 Years", "5 Years"],
        answer: "5 Years",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "How many types of state council of ministers?",
        options: [
          "Cabinet ministers",
          "State ministers",
          "Deputy ministers",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        answer: "All of the above",
        marks: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
  "Financial Education & Investment Awareness": {
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Expand GST?",
        options: [
          "Goods and saving tax",
          "Growth and service tax",
          "Goods and service tax",
          "Good and safe tax",
        ],
        answer: "Goods and service tax",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following are not a function of banks?",
        options: [
          "Agency and utility service",
          "Giving loans",
          "Acceptance and deposit",
          "Payment and withdraw",
        ],
        answer: "Agency and utility service",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "DBT stands for?",
        options: [
          "Direct Bank Transfer",
          "Direct Bank Transaction",
          "Direct Book Transfer",
          "Direct Benifit Transfer",
        ],
        answer: "Direct Benifit Transfer",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "NSDL stands for?",
        options: [
          "National Stock Defence Limited",
          "National Security Defence Limited",
          "National Securities Depository Limited",
          "None of these",
        ],
        answer: "National Securities Depository Limited",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "RBI Act was enacted in?",
        options: ["1951", "1937", "1934", "1944"],
        answer: "1934",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Intrest rates are fixed by ?",
        options: ["SBI", "RBI", "SEBI", "PSO"],
        answer: "RBI",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Current account are opened in?",
        options: ["Stock market", "Stock market", "Banks", "None of these"],
        answer: "Banks",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Full form of NPS?",
        options: [
          "National Provide Scheme",
          "National Pension scheme",
          "National problem schematic",
          "National Provide System",
        ],
        answer: "National Pension scheme",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Full form of PAN ?",
        options: [
          "Permanent Account Number",
          "Personal Account Number",
          "Physical Activity Number",
          "None of these",
        ],
        answer: "Permanent Account Number",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Adam Smith is the father of ?",
        options: ["Commerce", "Management", "Modern economic", "Zoology"],
        answer: "Modern economic",
        marks: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
  "Environmental Studies": {
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Natural selection was proposed by ?",
        options: ["Charles Darwin", "Aristotle", "odum", "Watson and Crick"],
        answer: "Charles Darwin",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Forest is what type of resource ?",
        options: [
          "Non renewable",
          "Renewable",
          "Both a and b",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "Renewable",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "By which of the following process plant are able to convert solar energy into chemical energy ?",
        options: [
          "Respiration",
          "Photosynthesis",
          "Transpiration",
          "Excretion",
        ],
        answer: "Photosynthesis",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the world largest desert ?",
        options: [
          "African Sahara desert",
          "Thar desert",
          "Arabian desert",
          "Gobi desert",
        ],
        answer: "African Sahara desert",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Expansion of CFC is ?",
        options: [
          "Carbon floride corporation",
          "Carbon functioning company",
          "Chlorofluorocarbon",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "Chlorofluorocarbon",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following unit is used to measure the sound ?",
        options: ["Watt", "Ohms", "Volts", "Decibel"],
        answer: "Decibel",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the percentage of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere ?",
        options: ["0.93%", "20.95%", "0.03%", "0.2%"],
        answer: "0.03%",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is an example for natural pollution ?",
        options: [
          "Volcanoes, cyclones and forest fire",
          "Chemicals released by the industries",
          "Pollution caused by insecticides",
          "None of the above",
        ],
        answer: "Volcanoes, cyclones and forest fire",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "National human rights commission head office is located at ?",
        options: ["Chennai", "Hyderabad", "Mumbai", "Delhi"],
        answer: "Delhi",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is an objective of family planning ?",
        options: [
          "To reduce birth rate",
          "To care for health of the child",
          "To reduce death rate",
          "All of the above",
        ],
        answer: "All of the above",
        marks: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
  "Cyber Security": {
    questions: [
      {
        question: "Which of the following is  an example of an input device?",
        options: ["Moniter", "Keyboard", "Printer", "Speakers"],
        answer: "Keyboard",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "What is the function of RAM in a computer ?",
        options: [
          "Long-term storge of data and programs",
          "Processing and executing instruction",
          "Providing power to the computer",
          "Storing frequently accessed data for quick retrieval by the CPU",
        ],
        answer:
          "Storing frequently accessed data for quick retrieval by the CPU",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which component of a computer is responsible for displaying visual output ?",
        options: ["CPU", "RAM", "Monitor", "Hard Disk Drive"],
        answer: "Monitor",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the purpose of and Operating System(OS) on a Computer ?",
        options: [
          "Storing and organizing files",
          "Running applications and managing hardware resources",
          "Providing physical protection to the computer",
          "Generating reports and documents",
        ],
        answer: "Running applications and managing hardware resources",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "What is the basic unit of data transmission over the internet ?",
        options: ["Byte", "Packet", "Megabyte", "Gigabyte"],
        answer: "Megabyte",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "",
        options: [
          "Creating dynamic animations",
          "Storing database",
          "Defining the structure and content of web pages",
          "Securing websites from cyber attacks",
        ],
        answer: "Defining the structure and content of web pages",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "Which of the following is an example of a professional social network ?",
        options: ["Facebook", "Instagram", "Linkedin", "Snapchat"],
        answer: "Linkedin",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is a mode of digital payment ?",
        options: [
          "Writing a check",
          "Swiping a credit card",
          "Using a mobile wallet app",
          "Exchanging physical currency",
        ],
        answer: "Using a mobile wallet app",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "What is UPI ?",
        options: [
          "A type of physical payment card",
          "An electronic fund transfer system in India",
          "A mobile operating system",
          "A social media platform",
        ],
        answer: "An electronic fund transfer system in India",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "What is a benefit od using UPI for payments ?",
        options: [
          "Limited compatibility with banks",
          "Higher transaction fee",
          "Longer processing times",
          "Instant and seamless fund transfers between bank accounts",
        ],
        answer: "Limited compatibility with banks",
        marks: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
  "Artificial Intelligence": {
    questions: [
      {
        question: "AI is abbreviated as ?",
        options: [
          "Aerial Intelligence",
          "Artificial Intelligence",
          "Anticraft Intelligence",
          "None of these",
        ],
        answer: "Artificial Intelligence",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "What is Artificial Intelligence ?",
        options: [
          "Putting yourself intelligence into computer",
          "Putting more memory into",
          "Programming with your own intelligence computer",
          "Making a machine intelligent",
        ],
        answer: "Making a machine intelligent",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "AI was established in the year__________?",
        options: ["1956", "1966", "1972", "1980"],
        answer: "1956",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question:
          "A persons ability to recognize and create sound, rhythm and sound pattern is known as_______ intelligence ?",
        options: ["Naturalist", "Interpersonal", "Musical", "Intrapersonal"],
        answer: "Musical",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "AI was coined by?",
        options: ["John Lee", "John Mc Carthy", "Richard", "None of the above"],
        answer: "John Mc Carthy",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following are the disadvantage of AI?",
        options: [
          "High cost",
          "Slow to implement practically",
          "Very few engineers available",
          "All the above",
        ],
        answer: "All the above",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Robotics institute in the USA is located at ?",
        options: ["SRI", "CMU", "RAND", "MIT"],
        answer: "CMU",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is the very first humanoid robot ?",
        options: ["Sophia", "ASIMO", "Pepper", "Romeo"],
        answer: "Sophia",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "The full form of NLG is?",
        options: [
          "Natural Language Gap",
          "Natural Language Group",
          "Natural Language Unity",
          "Natural Language Understanding",
        ],
        answer: "Natural Language Group",
        marks: 2,
      },
      {
        question: "Which of the following is not a application of robotics?",
        options: ["Medicine", "Industries", "Hills", "Military"],
        answer: "Hills",
        marks: 2,
      },
    ],
  },
};

export default topics;